http://www.e3media.co.uk/privacy

1 OverviewGreat State respect your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal data.This privacy policy (together with our Cookie Policy) explains how we look after your personal data when you visit our website (regardless of where you visit it from) and tell you about your privacy rights and how the law protects you.This website is not intended for children and we do not knowingly collect data relating to children.It is important that you read this privacy policy together with any other privacy notice or fair processing notice we may provide on specific occasions when we are collecting or processing personal data about you so that you are fully aware of how and why we are using your data. This privacy policy supplements the other notices and is not intended to override them.2 Data Controller2.1About use3 Media Limited, referred to as “we”, “us” or “our” in this privacy policy, is the data controller and is responsible for your personal data. e3 Media Limited (trading as Great State) is a brand technology agency, operating to provide digital services and products on behalf of our clients. Our registered company number is 3328177.To learn more about us, please see "Services".If you have any questions about this privacy policy, including any requests to exercise your legal rights, please contact us using the details set out below. We welcome questions, comments or requests concerning this privacy policy.As a company we take Data Protection and Cyber Security extremely seriously, this is not solely the responsibility of the IT team, it is the responsibility of the business, supported by the Senior Management Team. To support our commitment, we have invested in the following accreditations (certificates can be provided on request):ISO 270001: 2013Cyber EssentialsCyber Essentials PlusThe Cyber Club Gold Member2.2Contact detailsOur full details are:Full name of legal entity: e3 Media Limited, trading as Great StateContact: Brittany Child Email address: gdpr@greatstate.coPostal address: Unit 2.1 – 2.3, Paintworks, Bath Road, Bristol, BS4 3EHTelephone: 01179 021 333You have the right to make a complaint at any time to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO), the UK supervisory authority for data protection issues (www.ico.org.uk). We would, however, appreciate the chance to deal with your concerns before you approach the ICO so please contact us in the first instance.2.3Changes to the privacy policy and your duty to inform us of changesWe may make changes to this privacy policy at any time by sending an email to the last email address you gave us with the modified terms or by posting a copy of them on this website. Any changes will take effect 3 days after the date of our email or the date on which we post the changed policy on the site, whichever is the earlier. Your continued use of the site after that period expires means that you agree to be bound by the changed policy.It is important that the personal data we hold about you is accurate and current. Please keep us informed if your personal data changes during your relationship with us.2.4Third-party linksThis website may include links to third-party websites, plug-ins and applications. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control these third-party websites and are not responsible for their privacy statements. When you leave our website, we encourage you to read the privacy policy of every website you visit.3 What information do we collect about you?3.1 Personal dataPersonal data, or personal information, means any information about an individual from which that person can be identified. It does not include data where the identity has been removed (anonymous data). As part of Great State’s obligations to fulfil client contracts and operate as a business we collect various categories of Personal Data.We may collect, use, store and transfer different kinds of personal data about you which we have grouped together as follows:Identity Data includes first name, maiden name, last name, username or similar identifier, marital status, title, date of birth and gender.Contact Data includes billing address, delivery address, email address and telephone numbers.Financial Data includes bank account and payment card details.Transaction Data includes details about payments to and from you and other details of products and services you have purchased from us.Technical Data includes internet protocol (IP) address, your login data, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this website.Profile Data includes your interests, preferences, feedback and survey responses.Usage Data includes information about how you use our website, products and services.Marketing and Communications Data includes your preferences in receiving marketing from us and our third parties and your communication preferences.We also collect, use and share Aggregated Data such as statistical or demographic data for any purpose. Aggregated Data may be derived from your personal data but is not considered personal data in law as this data does not directly or indirectly reveal your identity. For example, we may aggregate your Usage Data to calculate the percentage of users accessing a specific website feature. However, if we combine or connect Aggregated Data with your personal data so that it can directly or indirectly identify you, we would still treat the combined data as personal data which will be used in accordance with this privacy policy.We do not collect any Special Categories of Personal Data about you (this includes details about your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, sex life, sexual orientation, political opinions, trade union membership, information about your health and genetic and biometric data). Nor do we collect any information about criminal convictions and offences.3.2 If you fail to provide personal dataWhere we need to collect personal data by law, or under the terms of a contract we have with you and you fail to provide that data when requested, we may not be able to perform the contract we have or are trying to enter into with you (for example, to provide you with goods or services). In this case, we may have to cancel a service we are providing you with, but we will notify you if this is the case at the time.4 How is your personal data collected?Direct interactions. You may give us your Identity, Contact and Financial Data by submitting information online via this website, filling in forms or by corresponding with us by post, phone, email or otherwise. This includes personal data you provide when you:subscribe to one of our services or publications;request marketing to be sent to you;enter a survey; orgive us some feedback.Automated technologies or interactions. As you interact with our website, we may automatically collect Technical Data about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns. We collect this personal data by using cookies and other similar technologies. Please see our cookie policy for further details.Third parties or publicly available sources. We may receive personal data about you from various third parties and public sources as set out below:Identity and Contact Data from publicly availably sources such as Companies House and the Electoral Register.5 How to we use your personal data?5.1 Legal basis for processingWe will only use your personal data when the law allows us to. Most commonly, we will use your personal data in the following circumstances:Where we need to perform the contract we are about to enter into or have entered into with you.Where it is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests. For example, where we are responding to you about your query.Where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation.Generally, we do not rely on consent as a legal basis for processing your personal data other than in relation to sending third party direct marketing communications to you via email or text message. You have the right to withdraw consent to marketing at any time by contacting us.5.2 Ways in which we use your personal dataWe have set out below, in a table format, a description of all the ways we plan to use your personal data, and which of the lawful bases we rely on to do so. We have also identified what our legitimate interests are where appropriate.Note that we may process your personal data on more than one lawful basis depending on the specific purpose for which we are using your data. Please contact us if you need details about the specific lawful basis we are relying on to process your personal data where more than one basis has been set out in the table below:Purpose/ActivityType of dataLawful basis for processing including basis of legitimate interestTo register you as a new client(a) Identity (b) ContactPerformance of a contract with youTo provide our marketing services including: (a) Managing payments, fees and charges (b) Collecting and recovering money owed to us(a) Identity (b) Contact (c) Financial (d) Transaction (e) Marketing and Communications(a) Performance of a contract with you (b) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to recover debts due to us)To manage our relationship with you which will include: (a) Notifying you about changes to our terms or privacy policy (b) Asking you to leave a review or take a survey(a) Identity (b) Contact (c) Profile (d) Marketing and Communications(a) Performance of a contract with you (b) Necessary to comply with a legal obligation (c) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to keep our records updated and to study how customers use our products/services)To administer and protect our business and this website (including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, system maintenance, support, reporting and hosting of data)(a) Identity (b) Contact (c) Technical(a) Necessary for our legitimate interests (for running our business, provision of administration and IT services, network security, to prevent fraud and in the context of a business reorganisation or group restructuring exercise) (b) Necessary to comply with a legal obligationTo deliver relevant website content and advertisements to you and measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve to you(a) Identity (b) Contact (c) Profile (d) Usage (e) Marketing and Communications (f) TechnicalNecessary for our legitimate interests (to study how customers use our products/services, to develop them, to grow our business and to inform our marketing strategy)To use data analytics to improve our website, products/services, marketing, customer relationships and experiences(a) Technical (b) UsageNecessary for our legitimate interests (to define types of customers for our products and services, to keep our website updated and relevant, to develop our business and to inform our marketing strategy)To make suggestions and recommendations to you about goods or services that may be of interest to you(a) Identity (b) Contact (c) Technical (d) Usage (e) ProfileNecessary for our legitimate interests (to develop our products/services and grow our business)To notify our customers if their users have contacted us.Necessary for our legitimate interests and those of our customers – allowing our customers to address requests regarding their users’ personal data.5.3 Promotional offers from usWe may use your Identity, Contact, Technical, Usage and Profile Data to form a view on what we think you may want or need, or what may be of interest to you. This is how we decide which products, services and offers may be relevant for you (“marketing”).You will receive marketing communications from us if you have requested information from us or instructed us to provide services and, in each case, you have not opted out of receiving that marketing.We will get your express opt-in consent before we share your personal data with any company outside Great State for marketing purposes.You can ask us or third parties to stop sending you marketing messages at any time by following the opt-out links on any marketing message sent to you or by contacting us at any time. Where you opt out of receiving these marketing messages, this will not apply to personal data provided to us as a result of other transactions.5.4 CookiesYou can set your browser to refuse some or all browser cookies, or to alert you when websites set or access cookies. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this website may become inaccessible or not function properly. For more information about the cookies we use, please see our Cookie Policy here.5.5 Change of purposeWe will only use your personal data for the purposes for which we collected it, unless we reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose. If you wish to get an explanation as to how the processing for the new purpose is compatible with the original purpose, please contact us.If we need to use your personal data for an unrelated purpose, we will notify you and we will explain the legal basis which allows us to do so.Please note that we may process your personal data without your knowledge or consent, in compliance with the above rules, where this is required or permitted by law.5.6 Who do we share your information with?We may have to share your personal data with the parties set out below for the purposes set out in the table above.Specific third parties such as Synergist (a centralised project management tool) see privacy policy here, Sage account and pay roll (Accounting and payroll system) see privacy policy here, Azure hosting solution, privacy policy here.Third parties for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.Third parties to whom we may choose to sell, transfer, or merge parts of our business or our assets. Alternatively, we may seek to acquire other businesses or merge with them. If a change happens to our business, then the new owners may use your personal data in the same way as set out in this privacy policy.We require all third parties to respect the security of your personal data and to treat it in accordance with the law. We do not allow our third-party service providers to use your personal data for their own purposes and only permit them to process your personal data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions.5.7 Where do we transfer your information?We do not transfer your information to, or store it in, countries located outside the European Economic Area (‘EEA’) which do not have as developed data protection laws.6 How do we keep your personal data secure?We have put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way, altered or disclosed. In addition, we limit access to your personal data to those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who have a business need to know. They will only process your personal data on our instructions and they are subject to a duty of confidentiality.We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so.All your information is stored on our secure servers, or on the servers of our suppliers.Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will apply our normal procedures and comply with legal requirements to protect your information, we cannot guarantee the security of your information transmitted to/from the site or on our behalf, and any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.Great State take a multi layered approach to protecting and securing access into our network and systems. This approach makes use of multiple best in class security services and components to protect our business systems and client data.The purpose of including multiple layers in your network security is to make sure that each single defence component has a backup in the case of a flaw or missing coverage. The individual strengths of each layer also cover any gaps that other defences may lack.Each individual layer in a multi-layered security approach focuses on a specific area where the malware could attack. By working in concert, these layers of security offer a better chance of stopping intruders from breaching company networks than using a single solution.The types of security layers we use in our network defence include, but are not limited to:Web ProtectionPatch Management (OS & 3rd Party Applications)Email Security and ArchivingEndpoint SecurityData EncryptionPerimeter & Endpoint FirewallsPerimeter & Endpoint Intrusion ProtectionDigital CertificatesRole Based Access Control (RBAC)Data Leak Protection (DLP)Application Control & Software RestrictionsDevice ControlAdvanced Threat Protection (ATP)We undertake several independent security assessments, run by National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC) approved CHECK/CREST testers, and hold multiple security compliance accreditations, which not only verifies our security approach, but also demonstrates our dedication and commitment to protecting our business and client's data.These include:ISO 27001Cyber Essentials PlusRegular Vulnerability AssessmentsPenetration TestingFirewall Configuration Reviews7 How long will we keep your personal data for?We will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.In some circumstances you can ask us to delete your data: see “request erasure” below for further information.In some circumstances we may anonymise your personal data (so that it can no longer be associated with you) for research or statistical purposes in which case we may use this information indefinitely without further notice to you.8 What are your rights?Under certain circumstances, you have rights under data protection laws in relation to your personal data:Request access to your personal data (commonly known as a “data subject access request”). This enables you to receive a copy of the personal data we hold about you and to check that we are lawfully processing it.Request correction of your personal data. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate data we hold about you corrected, though we may need to verify the accuracy of the new data you provide to us.Request erasure of your personal data. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove personal data where there is no good reason for us continuing to process it. You also have the right to ask us to delete or remove your personal data where you have successfully exercised your right to object to processing (see below), where we may have processed your information unlawfully or where we are required to erase your personal data to comply with local law. Note, however, that we may not always be able to comply with your request for erasure because of specific legal reasons which will be notified to you, if applicable, at the time of your request.Object to processing of your personal data where we are relying on a legitimate interest (or that of a third party) and there is something about your particular situation which makes you want to object to processing on this ground as you feel it impacts on your fundamental rights and freedoms. You also have the right to object where we are processing your personal data for direct marketing purposes. In some cases, we may demonstrate that we have compelling legitimate grounds to process your information which override your rights and freedoms.Request restriction on processing your personal data. This enables you to ask us to suspend the processing of your personal data in the following scenarios: (a) if you want us to establish the data’s accuracy; (b) where our use of the data is unlawful but you do not want us to erase it; (c) where you need us to hold the data even if we no longer require it as you need it to establish, exercise or defend legal claims; or (d) you have objected to our use of your data but we need to verify whether we have overriding legitimate grounds to use it.Request transfer of your personal data to you or to a third party. We will provide to you, or a third party you have chosen, your personal data in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format. Note that this right only applies to automated information which you initially provided consent for us to use or where we used the information to perform a contract with you.Right to withdraw consent where we are relying on consent to process your personal data. However, this will not affect the lawfulness of any processing carried out before you withdraw your consent. If you withdraw your consent, we may not be able to provide certain products or services to you. We will advise you if this is the case at the time you withdraw your consent.If you wish to exercise any of the rights set out above, please contact us.We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and ensure your right to access your personal data (or to exercise any of your other rights). This is a security measure to ensure that personal data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it. We may also contact you to ask you for further information in relation to your request to speed up our response.We try to respond to all legitimate requests within one month. Occasionally it may take us longer than a month if your request is particularly complex or you have made a number of requests. In this case, we will notify you and keep you updated.You will ordinarily not have to pay a fee to access your personal data (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive or excessive. Alternatively, we may refuse to comply with your request in these circumstances.
